Luis Rodriguez

Front End Developer



💌 rodluisr@gmail.com 🔭 luisrrv.com

in Luis Rodriguez 🔘 luisrrv

PROFILE

Born in Mexico and grew up in the US. I'm a 29 year old EE graduate turned in to a passionate web developer living in Tokyo. I enjoy designing and building responsive web applications. I'm also a big fan of European football.

I'm looking to bring my skills to a new position as a web developer at an international company that can allow me to grow and learn more skills.



Frontend Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React, SCSS

Backend Languages

Ruby, PostgreSQL, Ruby on Rails, MongoDB, GraphQL

Other

Git, Figma, AutoCAD, Photoshop



Japanese Language Proficiency **Test** N3



Spanish (Native) | English (Business)

Japanese (N3 Level)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Machine Designer, TOA Seiko

Aug 2021 - Mar 2022 | Tokyo, Japan

• Design industrial labor saving and automation machinery with CAD

Inventory Control / Shipping and Receiving,

Cactus Wellhead

Jan 2018 - Sep 2018 | Odessa, Texas, United States

- Perform visual inspection of incoming and outgoing products.
- Verify product receipts against BOL, product orders, and other shipping forms.
- · Work with drivers and warehouse workers to ensure safe unloading of product and compliance to general safety rules.

Quality Assurance Tester, TEK Systems

Jun 2017 - Jan 2018 | El Paso, Texas, United States

- Responsible for reporting and tracking issues.
- Write code/scripts to test systems and or controls.
- Ensure proper procedures and controls are in place throughout the testing process.

PROJECTS

AllyMaps, A trip planner for people with disabilities.

This app allows people with disabilities to plan entire accessible trips from searching places to the routes to and from the places in their itineraries.

Ninja Garage,

A marketplace where you can rent unique looking cars.

This app allows people to rent unique looking cars from the Japanese categories of "Itasha", "Bosozoku Bikes" and "Decotora".

Fantasy Dream Team,

An app where you can create your dream football team.

This app allows people to create teams with players of their choosing by selecting famous players and adding them to their custom teams.

EDUCATION

Akamonkai Japanese Language School

Oct 2018 - Mar 2020 | Tokyo, Japan

University of Texas at El Paso,

Bachelor of Science in Electrical and Computer Engineering |an 2014 - May 2017 | El Paso, Texas, United States

El Paso Community College, Associate of Arts

Aug 2011 - Dec 2013 | El Paso, Texas, United States